pyckio.com 2019-04-19

# Pyckio LegalLegal | Pyckio

Please find here our “Terms of use”, our “Code of Conduct” , our  “Privacy Policy”, our “Terms of Service” and our “Cookies Policy”

### \- TERMS OF USE -

In compliance with Law 34/2002, of July 11, on Services of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce (LSSI-CE), ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL informs that it owns the website WWW.PYCKIO.COM. In accordance with the requirement of article 10 of the aforementioned Law, ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL informs of the following information:

The owner of this website is ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, with CIF B86514338 and registered office at VIRGEN DE LLUCH, 5 28292, ENCINER I and II (LAS ZORRERAS) (MADRID), registered in the Mercantile Register, in volume 30132, folio 11, hojam-542355 and registration 1. The contact email address for the company is: support@pyckio.com.  
**User and responsibility regime**  
The navigation, access and use of the website of ONLINE SPORTs 2.0 SL confers the condition of user, by which they accept, from browsing the website of ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, all the conditions of use established here without prejudice of the application of the corresponding regulations of mandatory legal compliance as the case may be.  
The website of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL provides a great diversity of information, services and data. The user assumes his responsibility in the correct use of the website. This responsibility will extend to:  
 The veracity and legality of the information provided by the user in the forms extended by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL for access to certain content or services offered by the website.  
 The use of the information, services and data offered by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL contrary to the provisions of these conditions, the Law, morals, good customs or public order, or that in any other way may cause injury to the rights of third parties or the same functioning of the website.  
**Link policy and liability exemptions**  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL is not responsible for the content of the websites that the user can access through the links established on its website and declares that in no case will proceed to examine or exercise any type of control over the content of other sites in the network. Likewise, it will not guarantee the technical availability, accuracy, veracity, validity or legality of sites external to your property that can be accessed through the links.  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL declares to have adopted all the necessary measures to avoid any damage to the users of its website, which may arise from browsing its website. Consequently, ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL is not responsible, under any circumstances, for any damages that the user may suffer from Internet browsing.  
**Modifications**  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL reserves the right to make the modifications it deems appropriate, without prior notice, in the content of its website. Both with regard to the contents of the website, as in the conditions of use thereof, or in the general conditions of contract. Such modifications may be made through its website by any form admissible in law and  
they will be of obligatory fulfillment during the time in which they are published in the web and until they are not modified validly by later ones.  
**Online contracting services**  
Certain contents of the ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL website contain the possibility of contracting by Internet. The use of the same will require the reading and obligatory acceptance of the general conditions of hiring established for this purpose by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL.  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL informs that to make the online purchase will be redirected to the website.  
**Data Protection**  
In accordance with the regulations in force in Protection of Personal Data, we inform you that your data will be incorporated into the treatment system owned by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL with CIF B86514338 and registered office at VIRGEN DE LLUCH, 5 28292, ENCINAR I AND II (LAS ZORRERAS) (MADRID), with the purpose of facilitating, expediting and fulfilling the commitments established between both parties. In compliance with current regulations, ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL informs that the data will be kept for the period strictly necessary to comply with the aforementioned precepts.  
Until you tell us otherwise, we understand that your data has not been modified, that you agree to notify us of any variation and that we have your consent to use them for the purposes mentioned.  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL informs that it will proceed to treat the data in a lawful, loyal, transparent, adequate, pertinent, limited, exact and updated way. That is why ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL undertakes to adopt all reasonable measures so that these are suppressed or rectified without delay when they are inaccurate.  
In accordance with the rights conferred by the current regulations on data protection may exercise the rights of access, rectification

**SSL Certificate (Secure Sockets Layer)**  
The SSL CERTIFICATE provides authentication, privacy and information security between ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL and the user.  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL has a security certificate that is used by SSL CERTIFICATE to make secure connections.  
In this process several parameters are established to make the connection in a secure way and it is established using preset keys, coding and decoding all the data sent until the connection is closed.  
**Intellectual and industrial property**  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL by itself or as an assignee, is the owner of all the intellectual and industrial property rights of its website, as well as the elements contained in it (for example, images, sound, audio, video, software) or texts, trademarks or logos, combinations of colors, structure and design, selection of used materials, computer programs necessary for its operation, access and use, etc.), owned by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL. They will, therefore, works protected as intellectual property by the Spanish legal system, being applicable both Spanish and EU regulations in this field, as well as international treaties relating to the subject and signed by Spain.  
All rights reserved. Under the provisions of the Law on Intellectual Property, the reproduction, distribution and public communication, including its method of making available, all or part of the contents of this web page, for commercial purposes, are expressly prohibited. in any support and by any technical means, without the authorization of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL.  
The user undertakes to respect the Intellectual and Industrial Property rights owned by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL. You can visualize the elements of the portal and even print them, copy them and store them on your computer’s hard drive or on any other physical medium, as long as it is solely and exclusively for your personal and private use. The user must refrain from deleting, altering, evading or manipulating any protection device or security system that was installed on the pages of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL.  
**Legal actions, applicable legislation and jurisdiction**  
ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL also reserves the right to file civil or criminal actions it deems appropriate for the improper use of its website and content, or for the breach of these conditions.  
The relationship between the user and the provider will be governed by the regulations in force and applicable in Spanish territory. If any dispute arises, the parties may submit their disputes to arbitration or go to the ordinary jurisdiction, complying with the rules on jurisdiction and competence in this regard. ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL has its address in MADRID, Spain.

### \- CODE OF CONDUCT -

**Code of conduct**  
The user – member must accept these conditions of use and the contract conditions of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL, and must also comply with all applicable laws. You must use the platform correctly and respect the code of conduct established in this section, as well as take into account the regime of responsibilities established in the conditions of use and in the contracting conditions.  
In ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL we inform about the behaviors that we do not consider appropriate and act accordingly to the following uses, actions, omissions or statements that the mimbro performs, by virtue of the relationship that binds it to ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL:  
 Act dishonestly or unprofessionally.  
 Publish inappropriate or inaccurate content.  
 Harass, abuse, threaten or harm another person or user – member of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL.  
 Use or publish in ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL, through images, videos or any comment in the profile that may hurt the sensitivity of the user – members, as well as discriminate against any condition, race, ethnic group, nationality, religion , sex, sexual orientation, disability or illness, or that are illegal, insulting, abusive, obscene, discriminatory or for other causes considered to be reprehensible  
 Use the account of another person or create a false identity in ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL.  
 Make false statements that impersonate the identity.  
 Include content that contains computer viruses or others that can eliminate, interrupt or hinder the correct navigation of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL. -To sell, sponsor or obtain economic benefit through ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL without the authorization of ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL or if another method provided by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 SL has been established for the management of an exclusive service.  
 Share information of people who are not users – members without their express consent.  
**Rules of participation**

USER ACCOUNT  
For the registration of the account, the user must provide the data that are mandatory. The user will be the sole and exclusive responsible for the veracity of the data and the proportion of a valid email address whose ownership corresponds to it. The veracity of the data is important when it comes to facilitating the identification of forecasters or tipsters as well as for sending communications from Pyckio. Pyckio reserves the right to request additional data for the identification of the user for those cases in which it is necessary to verify the ownership of the account. In addition, Pyckio reserves the right to eliminate the account of those users who violate the rules of use of the website or who carry out activities that Pyckio considers to be detrimental to its image and reputation.  
During the registration process, the user must select a user name that will identify him on the website and to which the profile and the different activities for which the registration is required will be linked. The username must respect the following requirements:  
\- It can not contain words or expressions that are being used by other accounts that appear as active in the Pyckio systems.  
\- It may not contain words or expressions that are libelous, slanderous, infringing on industrial property rights of third parties, identification of third parties, both physical and legal, and, in general, that are contrary to law, morals or good customs.  
\- Pyckio reserves the right to delete any user names that contravene the requirements expressed above.  
In the same way, the user must choose a password. The user will be solely and exclusively responsible for the confidentiality and security of their password. The user undertakes to communicate as soon as possible the unauthorized use of their username and password or any unauthorized use that may have been made from their account. All activity carried out on the website with your password will be presumed to be carried out by the user and will also leave Pyckio harmless from any damage or loss that may arise from the non-compliance with the above requirements.  
In addition, the user may choose a profile image for the user account. This image may accompany the picks made or comments. The chosen image may not infringe intellectual or industrial property rights of third parties, impersonate other people’s identity, incite violence, racism or have a discriminatory or prejudicial nature against the honor, dignity or personal or family privacy of third parties. reasons of race, sex, nationality, religion or belief.  
The user will indemnify Pyckio against any liability that may arise from the use of a certain image.

###   
\- PRIVACY POLICY -

** **  
Pyckio is a sports betting international community which aims to allow tipsters to interact with bettors from all over the world through

(hereinafter, ‘the Website’) corresponding to the homepage of the Website. The use of the Website confers you the condition of a user of it and implies the full acceptance of the legal requirements included in this Privacy Policy.

Pyckio is committed to safeguarding your personal information as well as guaranteeing the correct processing of the data that you provide to us during the use of the Website. This Privacy Policy offers all the necessary information about the processing of data that Pyckio undertakes.

Pyckio reserves the right to amend and modify this Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to new legislation or case-law. You will be given advanced notice of these changes before its implementation. Once these changes have been announced, the use of our Service will imply its acceptance.

**Applicable Law**

This Website complies with all European and Spanish laws concerning the protection of personal data, particularly with the Spanish Data Protection Act 15/1999 (hereinafter, the ‘LOPD’), dated 13 December, and its enforcing regulation. Pyckio has implemented the technical and organizational measures to avoid the loss, misuse, variation, non-authorised access or data theft. These measures have been implemented according to the available technology, the nature of the data and the specific risks to which they are exposed.

**Security measures** ** **

We inform you that in regard to the processing of your data, Pyckio has implemented the security measures required by Spanish Royal Decree 1720/2007, dated 21 December, approving the Regulation that develop the LOPD (hereinafter, the ‘RLOD’). Moreover, Pyckio installs any other additional technical measures for avoiding the loss, misuse, variation, non-authorised access or data theft.

When the registration is required for using any of our Service, you may choose a personal password. You are the sole responsible for safeguarding the password you use to access the Services and for any activities or actions under your password. You agree to inform Pyckio as soon as possible about the non-authorised use of your User name and personal password or any malfunction within the security system. Pyckio will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from the failure to comply with the above.

**Data collection** ** **

You shall identify yourself in order to use the services provided at [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/). The required data shall be accurate and updated for the correct provision of the services.

Your data will be processed for the purpose of meeting your requests concerning, among others, the registration of picks, the participation in contests, general information, etc. Pyckio will solely process those data collected from you through the forms available at the Website or any other data which might be collected afterwards for the compliance of the purposes expressly indicated by you.

Your participation in the activities provided by the Website will require your registration and the creation of a user account. In this account, you shall introduce your username and the password requested during the signing up.

The current data processes made by Pyckio are the following ones:

-          **User account:** for getting an account you shall provide an e-mail address and select your country of residence. These data will be linked to your profile.

These data will be inputted to a personal data file registered by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0, S.L., at the Spanish Data Protection Agency. The submission of these data implies your full acceptance of this registration.

-          **Contact** : Whether you want to contact Pyckio for sending comments or enquiries about the Service, you shall provide your name or username and e-mail address. These data will be inputted to a personal data file registered by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 at the Spanish Data Protection Agency. The provision of your email address implies your full acceptance of this registration.

-          **Comments** : You have the possibility of sharing your ideas and comments to the different timelines by providing your name and e-mail address which will be inputted to a personal data file registered by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0 at the Spanish Data Protection Agency.

These data will not be transferred to third parties unless you have given your informed consent about the transfer and its purpose.

**Veracity of the data**

The personal information provided by you shall be accurate and current. You shall fill at least the required fields in the registration form. According to the Terms of Use, if you do not comply with this requirement, you will not be able to use the Service. ** **

Whether Pyckio has indications that the data is not accurate or whether it has to be completed, Pyckio reserves the right to require you additional information or to verify it using the method of contact you had previously provided for the registration or for filling the corresponding form.

You are responsible for the accuracy of the data provided to Pyckio and it is expressly forbidden the identity theft and the provision of third party data without its consent. Whether Pyckio becomes aware of the existence of identity theft, your user account will be deleted and we reserve the right to take the appropriate legal actions.  
**Publication of data**

Some information, like the username, might be seen by the rest of users in certain cases, for instance, during the publication of the pick. However, you can change or remove any information you have provided at any time except the picks which will remain visible for the other users.

**Communications**

Pyckio will contact with you via e-mail to the e-mail address you have provided in the corresponding field. You may oppose to the reception of such e-mails by sending a request to [support@pyckio.com](mailto:support@pyckio.com)

**Minors**

You shall be **18 years old** to use the services provided through [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/). Minors are not allowed to use our services.

**Social networks**

In accordance with the provisions of current legislation on Personal Data Protection (RGPD) and Law 34/2002, of July 11, Services of the Information Society and Electronic Commerce (LSSI-CE), ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL informs users that they have proceeded to create a profile in the Social Network / es / es Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Pinterest, Linkedin, Google +, with the main purpose of publicizing their products and services.  
Data of ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL: CIF: B86514338 ADDRESS: VIRGEN DE LLUCH, 5 28292, ENCINATE I AND II (LAS ZORRERAS) (MADRID) EMAIL: support@pyckio.com WEB DOMAIN: WWW.PYCKIO.COM  
The user has a profile in the same Social Network and has decided to join the page created by ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, showing interest in the information that is advertised on the Net. By joining our page, you provide your consent to the treatment of personal data published in your profile.  
The user can access the privacy policies of the Social Network at any time, as well as configure their profile to guarantee their privacy.  
ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL has access and deals with that public information of the user, especially his contact name. These data are only used within the Social Network itself. They are not incorporated into any file.  
In relation to the rights of access, rectification, limitation of treatment, deletion, portability and opposition to the treatment, of those that you have and that may be exercised before ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, in accordance with the RGPD, you must take into account the following nuances: Access: It will be defined by the functionality of the Social Network and the ability to access the information of user profiles. Rectification: It can only be satisfied in relation to that information that is under the control of ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, for example, eliminate comments published on the page itself. Normally, this right must be exercised before the Social Network. Cancellation and / or Opposition: As in the previous case, it can only be satisfied in relation to information that is under the control of ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, for example, no longer linked to the profile.  
ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL will perform the following actions: Access to public profile information. Publication in the user’s profile of all that information already published on the ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL page. Send personal and individual messages through the channels of the Social Network. Updates on the status of the page that will be published in the user’s profile.  
The user can always control their connections, remove the content that no longer interests them and restrict who shares their connections, for this they must access their privacy settings.  
PUBLICATIONS  
The user, once linked to the page of ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, may publish in the latter comments, links, images or photographs or any other type of multimedia content supported by the Social Network. The user, in all cases, must be the owner thereof, enjoy the copyright and intellectual property rights or have the consent of the affected third parties. It is expressly prohibited any publication on the page, whether texts, graphics, photographs, videos, etc. that attempt or are likely to attempt against morality, ethics, good taste or decorum, and / or that infringe, violate or violate the rights of intellectual or industrial property, the right to the image or the Law. In these cases , ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL reserves the right to immediately withdraw the content, being able to request permanent blocking of the user.  
ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL will not be responsible for the contents that a user has freely published.  
The user must keep in mind that his publications will be known by the other users, so he himself is the main responsible for his privacy.  
The images that can be published on the page will not be stored in any file by ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL, but they will remain in the Social Network.  
COMPETITIONS AND PROMOTIONS  
ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL reserves the right to carry out contests and promotions, in which the user may participate together with his page. The bases of each of them, when the platform of the Social Network is used for it, will be published in it. Always complying with the LSSI-CE and any other standard that applies to it.  
The Social Network does not sponsor, endorse or administer, in any way, any of our promotions, nor is it associated with any of them.  
ADVERTISING  
ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL will use the Social Network to advertise its products and services, in any case, if you decide to treat your contact data to perform direct commercial prospecting actions, it will always be in compliance with the legal requirements of the RGPD and the LSSI -EC.  
The fact of recommending the ONLINE SPORT 2 0 SL page to other users so that they can also enjoy the promotions or be informed of their activity will not be considered advertising.  
Below we detail the link to the privacy policy of the Social Network:  
“Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/help/323540651073243/  
“Twitter: https://twitter.com/privacy  
“Instagram: http://instagram.com/about/legal/privacy/  
“Pinterest: http://es.about.pinterest.com/terms/  
“Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=hb_ft_priv  
“Google +: http://www.google.com/intl/es/policies/privacy/

* * *

### \- TERMS OF SERVICE -

**Object** ** **

These Terms of Service describe the terms on which you may make use of the services provided by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0, S.L., including the navigation and participation at Pyckio. The reading of these Terms is a previous and necessary requirement for your participation on our website [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/).

Pyckio is an international Sports Betting community where tipsters like you submit their picks and, also, interact with other users. By using our Service, you will have the chance to become a PRO Tipster according to the goals and requirements established in the Website. ** **

We are not a bookmaker. We just provide you a platform for publishing yours and other Tipsters’ picks. Pyckio will not be liable for the use you give to the information published on our Website.

Terms of Service offers you the necessary information about some of the characteristics of the Service, such as the rules of participation. Your continued use of the Website indicates your full agreement without any reservation of the Terms.

**User account** ** **

It is necessary to have an account for participating in Pyckio. For obtaining this account you shall be, at least, 18 years old. Pyckio reserves the right to block or to delete those accounts of users who had not verified their age when it was requested.

You may follow the indications established in the Website, including the acceptation of the Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy.

Particularly, for the registration of the account you will have to provide the following information:

-          Username (between 3 and 15 characters, including letters and numbers) chosen by you during the registration.

-          E-mail address.

-          User password (with a minimum of 6 characters, including letters and numbers), chosen by you during the registration.

-          Country of residence.

-          Time zone

Moreover, you can voluntarily provide the following information to your profile:

-          Photography.

-          Name and surname (they will not be public).

-          Biography.

\-          Twitter account.

We will process these data in accordance with the conditions established in the Privacy Policy. You shall read and accept this Privacy Policy before using our Service.

**Participation** ** **

Once you have registered your account, you will be able to introduce your picks for free, according to the instructions published on the Website. These picks will be recorded on your profile. Furthermore, you can post comments which can be attached or not to the publication of a pick.

RATING

Users will be classified in accordance with the Rating and the Yield at the “Rankings” menu. Pyckio has developed an algorithm that provides the Rating and which determination depends principally on the following elements:

-          Yield (profit per amount bet).

-          Number of picks.

-          Average odds.

TIPSTER LEVELS

There are different Tipster levels, in accordance with the Rating:

-          Trainee

-          Rookie

-          Promise

-          Coach

-          Master

\-          GrandMaster

-          PRO

Users will start as Trainees by default. For reaching the next level you will have to comply with the requirements published on the Website. Notwithstanding that fact, Pyckio will give virtual medals to the best tipsters in certain sports or events during a specified period.

RANKING

Tipsters will be ranked regarding to 2 criteria: the yield or the rating. Only tipsters with positive records will appear in the Ranking. You will be able to access to the general Ranking or to a particular one of a certain sport.

CONTESTS

We will organize regular contests where you will have the possibility of wining several prizes. Any Pyckio registered user can take part in the contests. The legal basis of each contest will be published on the Website.

**Rules and guidelines**

USER ACCOUNT

You may follow any policies made available to you within the Service. For the registration, you may introduce the personal information required. You are responsible for the accuracy of that information and for the provision of a valid e-mail address. The accuracy of these data allows Pyckio to identify tipsters who take part in the Website. Pyckio reserves the right to require additional data for those cases where it is necessary to verify your identity.  Pyckio reserves the right to eliminate those accounts that breach our terms and conditions or that carry out activities that can damage the Pyckio image and reputation.

During the registration, you may select a username which will identify you in Pyckio and to which your personal profile and your activity will be associated. The username will have to respect the following requirements:

-          It may no content words or expressions which were used by another active Pyckio account that belongs to a third party.

-          It may no content words or expressions which may be considered injurious or defamatory, infringe Intellectual or Industrial Property Rights of a third party, identify a natural or a legal person, or be contrary to Law, moral standards or public order.

-          Pyckio reserves the right to delete any username selected in breach of the previous requirements.

You may also select a password for your account. You are the sole responsible for safeguarding the password you use to access to the Service and for any activities or actions under your password. You agree to inform Pyckio as soon as possible about the non-authorised use of your User name and personal password or any malfunction within the security system. Pyckio will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from the failure to comply with the above.

You may upload a profile picture for your account. This picture will be shown with your picks and comments and it may not infringe Intellectual or Industrial Property Rights of third parties; impersonate another person; encourage violence or racism; infringe upon the honour, dignity, personal or familiar intimacy of third parties, or discriminate on grounds of race, sex, nationality, religion or beliefs.

You will relieve Pyckio from liability for the use of the picture. Pyckio reserves the right to delete any picture which was in breach of the previous requirements.

If the user has the email notifications box checked in his/her settings, he/she will not mark as spam any of the emails sent by Pyckio. Otherwise, the user account will be automatically blocked and the user registered email will not be able to be used again at Pyckio. This policy is designed to protect us from the consequences that such an action could have in the service provided by our servers.

PICKS

You can submit your picks by choosing the sport, country, competition and particular match. Then, you will be able to select the game you want to tip on. Pyckio uses real time or with some seconds delay Pinnacle Sports odds. The odds are offered exclusively by Pinnacle Sports. Pyckio shall not be liable for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly from the odds published on the Website. _ _

It is not possible to submit a pick when you had already submitted a pick in the same market. Moreover, when you submit a pick the odd published on the Website might have changed. If so, an error message can appear and you will have to refresh the webpage to see the new odds and to submit your pick. ** **

You may also attach an explanation for your pick. This explanation may not contain words or expressions which may beconsidered injurious or defamatory, infringe Intellectual and Industrial Property Rights of a third party, correspond to a natural or a legal person, or be contrary to the Law, moral standards or public order. You will be the sole responsible for the content of the explanation. Pyckio reserves the right to block or to delete any explanation which was in breach of the previous requirements. ** **

COMMENTS

You may comment picks submitted by other tipsters. These comments may not:

-          Infringe these Terms of Service or the Law.

-         Promote violence or acts that may be considered defamatory, insulting or discriminatory on grounds of race, sex, nationality, religion, belief or age. ** **

**-    **       Contain words or expressions which may be considered injurious or defamatory, infringe Intellectual and Industrial Property Rights of a third party, correspond to a natural or a legal person, or be contrary to the Law, moral standards or public order.

-          Contain advertising messages which promotes products, services or commercial activities; predefined communications or any other type of messages whose object were not to issue opinions or information.

Pyckio reserves the possibility of delete any comment which was in breach of the previous requirements.

**Obligations of the parties**

Your obligations:

-          You may use the Service in accordance to these Terms of Service, the Law, the Good Faith, the moral standards and the public order.

-          You may not use the Service with illegal purposes that may be contrary to Pyckio’s interests or image including, without limitation, any action that may damage, render useless or overload the Website, or that may affect the contents in an inappropriate, illegal or fraudulent way.

-          You also undertake not to use the Service with the purpose of causing damage to the rights and interests of the rest of the users including, without limitation, to post comments or pictures that may be considered as inappropriate, illegal, racist, obscene, xenophobic, pornographic or defamatory.

-          You are the sole responsible for any contents which was uploaded by you.

-         You are the sole responsible for the accuracy of the data provided, including the username and the password. Any variation on the data shall be notified to Pyckio in order to provide the Service in a proper way.

-         You are responsible for the data provided, including the username and the password. Any action or step made under your password will be understood as made by you, regardless of the use of the account by a third party.

-         It is not allowed to use the Service with commercial, economic or any other purposes which were not considered in these Terms of Service or which were not expressly authorised by Pyckio.

-         It is required to be of legal age to use the Service.

Obligations of Pyckio:

-          Pyckio shall provide the complete information about the functioning of the Service.

-          Pyckio shall enable the participation and enjoyment of the Service by taking the necessary actions.

-          Pyckio shall enable a User Support Center with the purpose of attending to any enquiry, request or claim that may be brought by a tipster.

**User Support Center and communications**

Any claim or request of information about the functioning, quality or any other issue related to the Website may be sent to the User Support Center as soon as you have noticed it. You can contact Pyckio through the “Contact” link available at [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/)

The same procedure shall be followed in case you want to contact Pyckio for any issues related to the provision of the Service, its execution or any other event you deem appropriate. ** **

Once the claim or request has been attended, Pyckio will use all available means to inform you about the solution adopted by using the same method of contact you had previously used.

**Liability**

TERMS OF SERVICE

You may be liable for any breach of the obligations that you have accepted by visiting the Website. Pyckio shall not assume nor accept any liability for any loss or damage caused to a third party because of your use of the Website.

PROVISION OF THE SERVICE

In no event shall Pyckio be liable for the existence of interruptions, temporary inability of access, problems with the availability of the contents or its defects, or the damages that you may suffer because of its use. Pyckio cannot guarantee neither the infallible provision of the Service nor the continuous access to its webpage or third-parties contents.

LINKS

This Website may contain hyperlinks to websites or resources operated by third parties. Pyckio will not accept any responsibility or liability for any third-party websites and resources and your use of such services and contents must be done at your own risk under its terms of use.

THIRD PARTIES CONTENTS

In certain circumstances, you are allowed to submit your own content such as comments or pictures which will be hosted on the Website. You will be the sole responsible for these contents and Pyckio does not warrant, endorse, guarantee or assume responsibility for them. The publication of this comments and photos shall remain subject to these Terms of Service, whose compliance will depend exclusively on you:

-          You declare that you are the owner or licensee of such contents published on the Website and, therefore, you hold the right to assign the Intellectual and Industrial Rights of these contents to Pyckio.

-          Pyckio will not be liable for any judicial or extrajudicial claim concerning the contents that may be brought against us.

Pyckio reserves the right to withdraw or to block the access to those contents that may be seen as illegal or that may injure goods or rights of a third party.

PICKS

Picks are submitted by your own and sole responsibility. Pyckio does not warrant, endorse, guarantee or assume responsibility for the totality, accuracy or usefulness of the picks. Picks will be published in accordance to the Rules of Participation. Pyckio reserves the right to withdraw those picks which were in breach of the Rules of Participation.

We inform you that the odds are established by Pinnacle Sports and Pyckio does not have any control over them. Pyckio shall not be liable for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly from the odds published on the Website.

**Intellectual and Industrial Property** ** **

We or, where appropriate, the author, the rights holder or its licensor declare that Pyckio is the exclusive owner or grantee of the whole Website, including its design, structure, layout, texts and contents, logotypes, trademarks, Web buttons, images, drawings, source code, and any other Intellectual or Industrial Property rights or distinctive signs. The authorisation for the use of the Website shall not be deemed as a waiver of such rights.

You will retain the ownership rights about the content you have uploaded. By uploading this content you grant Pyckio a worldwide, non-exclusive, royalty-free, sublicenseable and transferable license to use, reproduce, distribute, display or transform it according to the technical needs of Pyckio for the maximum extent permitted under the applicable Law.

** ** **Privacy** ** **

Pyckio is committed to safeguarding your privacy. All the personal data and any other personal information collected from you will be treated in accordance to the terms of the Privacy Policy.

Pyckio reserves the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy in order to adapt it to new legislation or case-law. You will be given a reasonable advanced notice of these changes before its implementation. Once these changes have been announced, the use of our Service will imply its acceptance.

GOVERNING LAW

This Website complies with all European and Spanish laws concerning the protection of personal data, particularly with the Spanish Data Protection Act 15/1999 (hereinafter, the ‘LOPD’), dated 13 December, and its enforcing regulation. Pyckio has implemented the technical and organizational measures to avoid the loss, misuse, variation, non-authorised access or data theft. These measures have been implemented according to the available technology, the nature of the data and the specific risks to which they are exposed.

SECURITY MEASURES ** **

We inform you that in regard to the processing of your data, Pyckio has implemented the security measures required by the Spanish Royal Decree 1720/2007, dated 21 December, approving the Regulation developing the LOPD (hereinafter, the ‘RLOPD’). Moreover, Pyckio installs any other additional technical measures for avoiding the loss, misuse, variation, non-authorised access or data theft.

When the registration is required for using any of our services, you may choose a personal password. You are the sole responsible for safeguarding the password you use to access to the Service and for any activities or actions under your password. You agree to inform Pyckio as soon as possible about the non-authorised use of your username and personal password or any malfunction within the security system. Pyckio will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from the failure to comply with the above.

DATA COLLECTION

According to the Privacy Policy, your personal information will be inputted to a personal data file registered by ONLINE SPORTS 2.0, S.L., at the Spanish Data Protection Agency. Certain information is needed to offer you the Service, so the data you provide shall be accurate. The submission of these data implies your full acceptance of this registration.

Pyckio will use your personal information for the provision of the Service through [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/) and, in case you check the corresponding boxes at the section ‘E-mail notifications’ you will receive alerts for the picks posted by other tipsters and news and information about the Service.

These data will not be transferred to third parties unless it was necessary for the provision of the Service and you had given your informed consent about the transfer and its purpose.

You may exercise your right to access, rectify, cancel and oppose to the data, by informing ONLINE SPORTS 2.0, S.L., through [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/) or by sending a letter to 28290 Las Rozas, Madrid, Calle Rozabella 6, Edificio París, planta baja, nº 9.

**Changes to the Terms of Service** ** **

Pyckio may amend or modify these Terms of Service at any time and without notice. You will be informed about these changes at least one (1) month before the changes become effective. ** **

These changes may be done by any legal means and they will be compulsory for you since they were published on the Website. These changes will not affect any action taken before they were approved.

**Waiver and severability** ** **

If any provision of these Terms of Service is deemed or at any time becomes illegal, invalid or unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the legality, validity or enforceability of the remaining provisions of these Terms of Service, which shall remain in full force and effect.

No waiver of any term of this these Terms of Service shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and Pyckio’s failure to assert any right or provision under these Terms of Service shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.

**Governing Law and Jurisdiction** ** **

These Terms of Service shall be governed by the Spanish Law. Any claim or dispute between you and Pyckio arising in whole or in part from the provision of the Service shall be decided exclusively by a court of competent jurisdiction located in Madrid (Spain). Whether you have the condition of a consumer, the jurisdiction will be established according to the Consumer legislation.

### \- COOKIES POLICY -

**1\. General Information**

This Website uses cookies to improve your experience during the provision of the Service. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer’s browser directory or on your personal device when you visit [www.pyckio.com](http://www.pyckio.com/). These files cannot damage your devices. Cookies allow the webmaster to store and to recover information about your use of the Website in order to improve the quality of the Service.

The object of the implementation of the cookies is to provide a proper performance of the Website. Without cookies enabled we cannot guarantee that the provision of the Service whilst visiting the Website is as we intended to be. Additionally, cookies allow your preferences to be collected and to obtain information about your experience.

The information below will help you to understand the different types of cookies used by Pyckio. ** **

**2\. Types, purpose and functioning**

Cookies used by Pyckio can be classified under several criteria:

  1. According to the responsible of its management

a. According to the responsible of the management of the system or device from which the cookies are sent, it is possible to distinguish:

-          First-Party cookies: those cookies sent to your device from a system managed by Pyckio. The information collected will be processed exclusively by Pyckio.

-          Third-party cookies: Third-party cookies are cookies that have been written on to your device by a different website from Pyckio. Cookies which are sent from a system or device managed by Pyckio have also this condition if the information collected is processed by a third party (for instance, when you click on the icon of a social network or when you play a video hosted on our site). That information will not be accessible for Pyckio.

b. According to its length or duration

According to its lifetime, cookies can be classified as:

-          Session cookies: these are temporary cookies, which only exist until you close the browser after the access to the Website. These cookies help Pyckio to track your actions in our Website and, therefore, to avoid the need to re-enter the information you have previously provided.

-          Persistent cookies: these are cookies, which are stored on your device and which are read every time you access the Website. These cookies will remain on your device until its expiry date. We inform you that all the cookies have an expiry date which establishes its lifetime.

c. According to its purpose

According to the purpose of the cookies we can distinguish:

-          Technical cookies: these are cookies which allow you to browse through the Website and to use the different options and Services offered by Pyckio. For instance, using such cookies Pyckio can monitor the traffic of the web and the transfer of information, identify your session, register a user, use security tools during your browse, etc. These cookies are necessary for the proper performance of the site.

-          Analytic cookies: these cookies enable Pyckio to quantify the number of users who visit the Website and how do they use it. This information is used to conduct statistical analysis on the use of our Website.

-          Customization cookies: these cookies enable you the access to the Website with some settings established by default such as the language, the type of browsing and the regional configuration.

-          Functional cookies: these cookies support our Website function and its Services and, for instance, allow you to share any particular content.

**3\. List and description of cookies**

** ** Tables published below set out the information about cookies used at the Website by Pyckio:

**** ** You can allow, block or delete the cookies installed in your device by modifying the options available at the browser settings. You can get more information by clicking in the links below: **     **4\. Browser settings**

  * For further information about Microsoft Internet Explorer, click [here](http://windows.microsoft.com/es-es/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies)
  * For further information about Mozilla Firefox, click [here](https://support.mozilla.org/es/kb/habilitar-y-deshabilitar-cookies-que-los-sitios-we)
  * For further information about Google Chrome, click [here](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=es)
  * For further information about Safari, click [here](http://support.apple.com/kb/ph5042)
